

PROFILE

Spirited and outspoken IT specialist, with a taste for art, organisation, and human development.

Enthusiast of many fields and disciplines, with a knack for communicating in a plain friendly manner suitable for non-specialist.

But ultimately, a man on a mission to create places of joy in life & work.

INFO

Country of Residence: Venezuela

Willing to Relocate: Yes_

Phone No. +58 (412) 293 33 90

Email:

jaykozatt@gmail.com

Portfolio: jaykozatt.github.io

Blog: jaykozatt.medium.com

JAY KOZATT

Gameplay Programmer

EXPERIENCE

Team Lead / Programmer as Independent Team SEPTEMBER 2021 - CURRENT

- Organised the project structure following agile methodologies.
- Co-designer of game mechanics.
- Designed and implemented systemic gameplay solutions.
- Both directed and worked on art design in our team's projects..
- Acquired limited sound mixing experience with FMOD Studio.

Tech Specialist @ Studio Dread

MAY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Lead tech specialist at budding indie studio under revshare model.
- Spearheaded a significant part of the initial organisation efforts of the team, and the project structure.
- Assessed and reviewed game design decisions.
- In charge of implementing core game mechanics & systems.

Student Assistant @ BWL Teachers' Lab

Universidad Simón Bolívar JAN 2020 - CURRENT

- Reorganised the lab's student personnel into a proper working structure.
- Developed the team's skills through workshops in several domains.
- Provided tech support for the lab on a need-basis.

EDUCATION

Computation Engineering at Universidad Simón Bolívar Caracas, Venezuela

TECH PROFICIENCIES

Game Engines	Unity Engine RPG Maker VX Ace
Image Manipulation Software	Illustrator Photoshop Aseprite
Programming Languages	C#, C++, C Ruby Python
Database Managers	PostgreSQL SQLite 3